<xml xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <tab name="init" type="InitTab" active="false" scrollx="1104" scrolly="555.3928709635534" scale="0.8999999999999999"></tab>
  <tab name="main" type="MainTab" active="true" scrollx="2126.123246462834" scrolly="366.578200940035" scale="0.5387568978066388">
    <variables xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml">
      <variable id=":+7+5;kQPfZw!cZ{ae{+">OffOn</variable>
    </variables>
    <block xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml" type="setMaterialColor" id="SQxpM(gbM[nUfv*Ari]G" x="-5510" y="-350">
      <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" flexcolinput="false" usecsscolor="false"></mutation>
      <field name="MAT_COL_NAME">Principled BSDF Color</field>
      <value name="MATERIAL">
        <shadow type="materialList" id="WTbF}Klx+h惕竿沓裘⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰浦兵搅笆鹦岸每酆握⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰袭麒守厮廨廊槐另缬⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰丹如鲳摸雕聒羊秃懊冖兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦敉狒弪獒烀镬矧殇舰裢莴外皖阐鲼葚轿微柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱骒屮泔扉铕豸舰驷祗澧躞邈篌泔祜蚪㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰土赃孟踢瘟团⒕序轭汩痨邃掠钠蔑祜蚣骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰土耘疑撂⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰蹦雎疔掠‖俘湄陈麦⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤布骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰畏二肉隧濉鸦条°唁盯兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰璇琼镭甾脍唿躬菖⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰戴寝丢藐び煅卦儆砝涪兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰訾吞＃勖印诙荬洵惆傣⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰韩帆祷胙墟邝°邴徨⒕湘嫦罴骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰夥肃吊孑嵩猹乳鸪等恝兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶盱铙舰梏麴蠛溴鲥祜疱蝮顼镧戾泔懑忪镢腱盱豉疱舰弼孱羧酝膛戾恝殇舰呃予柏台括唷仍璜痘畀舰彻卑舰吵阿兼殄熹钺礤舰胖盼寓俱扉汶集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰辛遗卧⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰赡⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰殷贝犁麟炝抑猬杵注兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕湘嫦罴骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰泔铘蝻祗唛驽祗澧殇舰妍似踌宸递跋闯芭测刷荐犰蹂钺礤舰善阿尖祜汶豉疱舰祜玳氵泔眇狎澧殇舰绲阐醣盹寸鑫ㄛ筠微兼殄熹钺礤舰闲⒕叛集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰立尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮珏簪殇舰瑛ニ乔蛳嗟冤曛鳙丽⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰韩帆祷胙墟邝°邴徨⒕湘嫦罴骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰醮快愎淫９橛忾无仵⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南阿尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰人铕遒阵谊ク已幸菠穗⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰韩帆祷胙墟邝°邴徨⒕湘嫦罴骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰？强盂路驴劾旬遇骢先⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷颈集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰狍箝珙歪翦蜷犰殇舰幻舄糈穗疹瘾ｃＺ娉幄荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶挪⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰樘猾莨禽悲笱鲎似丁脚⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞居泸邋湘婕骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶疟⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰猱陉贸惕挠赵种垒傣纬⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞倔泸邋罴骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰盘优⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰鲠蜷徕戾筮箦簪殇舰蛞蚌耨猹咤岫腆洱幄兼殄熹钺礤舰至尧殇舰韩帆祷胙墟邝°邴徨⒕湘嫦罴骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶泞尖祜汶豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰韩怙畎醵沙马鄄旮瀵孩兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景集骈屐渚集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰狍箝珙歪翦蜷犰殇舰罪婺劫笮襁浴琶怖殿啄⒕荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶挪⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰薷昶疼诼杨森犒暑糠鳍兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞居泸邋项集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰至陶疟⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰昀嗣膘胭晌含派叮Ｙ⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞倔泸邋罴骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶盱铙舰梏麴蠛溴鲥祜疱蝮顼镧戾泔懑忪镢腱盱豉疱舰弼孱羧酝膛戾恝殇舰昂睬岑证若莨铮熙茛舰巢钒舰吵并兼殄熹钺礤舰胖盼寓俱扉汶集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰辛遗卧⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰赡⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰俄黯魂铁诎搭邹シ锕≥⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕蚂徙爰骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦敉狒弪獒烀镬矧殇舰仪蚱蜢锰讽筠娑⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱骒屮泔扉铕豸舰驷祗澧躞邈篌泔祜蚪㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰土赃孟踢瘟团⒕序轭汩痨邃掠钠蔑祜蚣骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰土耘疑撂⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰垦曼８狻甭古榛屯囱ア兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰醑ｒ铤混戛谀臭压信耽兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰òト扑嗖慧甍倏卸单ア兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰韵淙咸专绣捶顶燎寨挞兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦敉狒弪獒烀镬矧殇舰≮猴厚厍伊怀珐戈呷溺⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱骒屮泔扉铕豸舰驷祗澧躞邈篌泔祜蚪㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰土赃孟踢瘟团⒕序轭汩痨邃掠钠蔑祜蚣骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰土耘疑撂⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰顷流噻唪谄蛲鬣沛愧兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤布骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰蜜施啾狠猾美意参掐⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰埔吞喝傍骁０祆递洹班⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰绞岁骆羧叛锩兵铕颜并兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景氨膊狈集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶盱铙舰梏麴蠛溴鲥祜疱蝮顼镧戾泔懑忪镢腱盱豉疱舰弼孱羧酝膛戾恝殇舰氪玲惶麦骠熄兆卜虏愧舰档蛋舰钡阿兼殄熹钺礤舰胖盼寓俱扉汶集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰辛遗卧⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰赡⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰飓磔橼碇圹傥胼孱＊⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕箩汶集骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰彰倍柴剑怔鐾蹲钢水脾柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞弼邈麸蝮祜艚㈡犰箦躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰掀朴旁⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰爷嗍痼摇虞裤…卜聪绀⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞久犴弪峒骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰丌尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰秉背豆芥饯蹲尺并柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑绝集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰剔哟暗蝽弁颖埋Ｍ参幄兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰佗尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰磁∨杖厝ヌ默ヤ龀打⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑均集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰椁划蓦诿骛亟泵铠赢⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰冖尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰戕耨惴盼橄枚谛段恽柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑菌集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰嶙赈迕毕哼屺友岜注兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰噤┾鲺飑纫孚俐污寸⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞弼邈麸蝮祜艚㈡犰箦躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕蝻翎糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰掀朴旁⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰檄昌廨务甬漉懊鹨龈袁⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞久犴弪峒骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰丌尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰嗌丛迈恍币锅嵌扯腰⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕蝻翎糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑绝集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰悫兵パ瘾臌ˉ窠ǒ⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰佗尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰企屦肟揉】嗵玻龃晔簪柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕蝻翎糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑均集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰瑟潆錾珏编茵猕迥肼纰兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰冖尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰趺兕笠佟菪茂戡保寓柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕蝻翎糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑菌集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰哗呓每螽茹è赉ゐ舰兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘录骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶盱铙舰梏麴蠛溴鲥祜疱蝮顼镧戾泔懑忪镢腱盱豉疱舰弼孱羧酝膛戾恝殇舰馋篪鹈洮潼蜣胀牙露廷舰巢钒舰钡阿兼殄熹钺礤舰胖盼寓俱扉汶集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰辛遗卧⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰赡⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰翎拖衅往腱昏鬼ē珠螈兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕阻轸寮骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦敉狒弪獒烀镬矧殇舰圃Ｃ浙楂背ǐ竺闼轸⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱骒屮泔扉铕豸舰驷祗澧躞邈篌泔祜蚪㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰土赃孟踢瘟团⒕序轭汩痨邃掠钠蔑祜蚣骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰土耘疑撂⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰赛捭汔踵─铍量哔柴丌兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰二劣攘屺遄ǎ灶堪做⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰阢痨诤拐漆裨礞氐蛰⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰诖行显颃Ｋ锑镏ぁ芒兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦敉狒弪獒烀镬矧殇舰煺磲溴尹扪鄢庆妪佗柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱骒屮泔扉铕豸舰驷祗澧躞邈篌泔祜蚪㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰土赃孟踢瘟团⒕序轭汩痨邃掠钠蔑祜蚣骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰土耘疑撂⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翦蜷犰涕篝殇舰致埤西仍┳壅缒铰圜⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞韭镤布骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰尧俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰讲法愎洙字濂埤么谦廷兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰洽俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰嚅晷腱铑ㄑ噶沭簋伢储兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰垄俭栳滹豉疱舰磲翳哳蹴忮颌殇舰滩署ゆ珲蒸死珲佑甸⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰握廷景钩氨奔骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集铄艟集忪镢刖集篝狒屙孱艟集忪镢刖尖祜汶盱铙舰梏麴蠛溴鲥祜疱蝮顼镧戾泔懑忪镢腱盱豉疱舰弼孱羧酝膛戾恝殇舰旮鳝团檩酿鳄┊琪菠舰档蛋舰蛋⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰胖盼寓俱扉汶集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰辛遗卧⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰赡⒕俭栳滹豉疱舰翦簪殇舰宴沭莅惭邸珐凶か痃澧兼殄熹钺礤舰耘卦⒕骑蝼狎浼骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰俭翎翦礤铘钺礤舰南⒕尖祜汶豉疱舰箦粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰岫钚迸瞍描钍苞湓卯⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞弼邈麸蝮祜艚㈡犰箦躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰掀朴旁⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰奥碲哓锨蛀贤ㄥ挛辙嘣⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞久犴弪峒骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰丌尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰阗匦埒祟瑶簋嵫乱止⒕柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑绝集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰牙疑渊鳏崛沼哦企讳洧兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘良骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰佗尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰陌梯族蝥℃年隳缌螈柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑均集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰坤仳眩兑持忪傻蚩┛诞⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘良骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰冖尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰金ｏ裔溘迨韫氵裘腴息柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕痫箝糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰孟弦蘑菌集骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰膏＄伙葸块幸波┟璐⒕兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞拘镩铘良骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰集忪镢刖集鲠祯寰碱屮艟尖祜汶豉疱舰箦粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰ǜ傍阻蜕迮恩诘结蒂蔻柬豸狒轱盱铙舰梏麴函鼢鳟鞒矧绡惫构梏盱躞弼邈麸蝮祜艚㈡犰箦躞鬻矧熹箴徙褰㈡犰箦⒕集眭翎糸镱兼殄熹钺礤舰拖呐⒕蝻翎糸镱集骈屐渚兼殄熹钺礤舰掀朴旁⒕屏逃偶骈屐渚荐犰蹂钺礤舰粤仪旁下盛俭栳滹豉疱舰镡赍泗涕篝殇舰筢麾榍噬腩卧份忮鳍兼殄熹钺礤舰粕盘奈镣泞久犴弪峒骈屐渚集箬徜秣集鲠祯寰荐犰蹂钺礤舰丌尖祜汶豉疱舰珏粝怅则犷箧矧恝殇舰邾蔓摈ǖ区膏痕梆t[">
                  <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" useworldspace="false"></mutation>
                  <field name="MODE">rotation</field>
                  <field name="COORD">x</field>
                  <value name="TARGETOBJ">
                    <shadow type="objectList" id="kvV^1U;CBk2vsK95w3Un">
                      <field name="FIELDNAME">Point A</field>
                    </shadow>
                  </value>
                </block>
              </value>
              <value name="Y">
                <block type="getObjTransform" id="FPdK#SOy4b%0?xOGB!oP">
                  <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" useworldspace="false"></mutation>
                  <field name="MODE">rotation</field>
                  <field name="COORD">y</field>
                  <value name="TARGETOBJ">
                    <shadow type="objectList" id="%=2rMN`U.PkiZeg?iAV,">
                      <field name="FIELDNAME">Point A</field>
                    </shadow>
                  </value>
                </block>
              </value>
              <value name="Z">
                <block type="getObjTransform" id="TSPXR[8]jTrTZKA.=iCL">
                  <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" useworldspace="false"></mutation>
                  <field name="MODE">rotation</field>
                  <field name="COORD">z</field>
                  <value name="TARGETOBJ">
                    <shadow type="objectList" id="mpoY`a`Fe9g.*SJ*!qS+">
                      <field name="FIELDNAME">Point A</field>
                    </shadow>
                  </value>
                </block>
              </value>
            </block>
          </next>
        </block>
      </statement>
    </block>
    <block xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml" type="eventHTMLElem" id="(|(Dryj-Dg_;cg;b}a]" x="-3270" y="10">
      <field name="EVENT">click</field>
      <field name="PARENT">FALSE</field>
      <value name="ID">
        <shadow type="text" id="lR)=ro7(AN@XmN_Bt4T_">
          <field name="TEXT">Blue</field>
        </shadow>
      </value>
      <statement name="DO">
        <block type="setMaterialColor" id="bMz3Tp-7_r/zebq`57*1">
          <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" flexcolinput="false" usecsscolor="false"></mutation>
          <field name="MAT_COL_NAME">Principled BSDF Color</field>
          <value name="MATERIAL">
            <shadow type="materialList" id="+nb8th%P1!n]DneATc9:">
              <field name="FIELDNAME">Body 1</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="R">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="l+whVpV*YG`:_27t6V{x">
              <field name="NUM">0.693871</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="G">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="p?V0K19}tEfl+}P+h_q">
              <field name="NUM">0.822785</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="B">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="]EIRdt|N4N642l/?(pP">
              <field name="NUM">0.955973</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <next>
            <block type="setMaterialColor" id="0Sp}=TRO4G3@j)QB8tc2">
              <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" flexcolinput="false" usecsscolor="false"></mutation>
              <field name="MAT_COL_NAME">Principled BSDF Color</field>
              <value name="MATERIAL">
                <shadow type="materialList" id="#T_GlJo%^7b803)rN2PU">
                  <field name="FIELDNAME">Body 2</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="R">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="FoYqikQs-?uETWz0LciX">
                  <field name="NUM">0.693871</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="G">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="t{/?GZI2+:/#%hLaAD:]">
                  <field name="NUM">0.822785</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="B">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="fPJuNN}NN^(ssAH);v7}">
                  <field name="NUM">0.955973</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
            </block>
          </next>
        </block>
      </statement>
    </block>
    <block xmlns="https://developers.google.com/blockly/xml" type="eventHTMLElem" id="#/9pdu4|V^,imXf_O`9Q" x="-3270" y="170">
      <field name="EVENT">click</field>
      <field name="PARENT">FALSE</field>
      <value name="ID">
        <shadow type="text" id="b`Wa+e)k#:aSyJ!tyLz0">
          <field name="TEXT">Peach</field>
        </shadow>
      </value>
      <statement name="DO">
        <block type="setMaterialColor" id="B5Q$=qEeLc_7lLz4,_8%">
          <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" flexcolinput="false" usecsscolor="false"></mutation>
          <field name="MAT_COL_NAME">Principled BSDF Color</field>
          <value name="MATERIAL">
            <shadow type="materialList" id="Zk18Ecfi-Iq.bq}n)">
              <field name="FIELDNAME">Body 1</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="R">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="h[4K.|ke{hW[+S{K-m2.">
              <field name="NUM">0.938685</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="G">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="9cCU2Kg[PuiXQgET1sn$">
              <field name="NUM">0.672443</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <value name="B">
            <shadow type="math_number" id="[Ax]+2utQFSdi@^@.zd">
              <field name="NUM">0.496933</field>
            </shadow>
          </value>
          <next>
            <block type="setMaterialColor" id="(uWI;|T5Cr%XR:YqjIux">
              <mutation xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" flexcolinput="false" usecsscolor="false"></mutation>
              <field name="MAT_COL_NAME">Principled BSDF Color</field>
              <value name="MATERIAL">
                <shadow type="materialList" id="wHBw63lER@8ut/C7gqI">
                  <field name="FIELDNAME">Body 2</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="R">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="T5Wd.5@Q]#Lwk@O5RQjK">
                  <field name="NUM">0.938685</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="G">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="zq#`nPE27w!j5|Ns/B+m">
                  <field name="NUM">0.672443</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
              <value name="B">
                <shadow type="math_number" id="^W7%l^7^NXU;6d]TLtf">
                  <field name="NUM">0.496933</field>
                </shadow>
              </value>
            </block>
          </next>
        </block>
      </statement>
    </block>
  </tab>
  <editorsettings viewport-x="869.3333129882812" viewport-y="28" viewport-w="392.667" viewport-h="213.667" viewport-hidden="false" toolbox-library-mode="false" toolbox-minimized-mode="false"></editorsettings>
</xml>